Speaker 1: Mary?
Speaker 0: Hi.
Speaker 0: Hello.
Speaker 1: I'm Susan Thompson, resource manager.
Speaker 0: Hi.
Speaker 0: I'm Mary Hansen, and I'm applying for one of your kitchen jobs.
Speaker 0: Great.
Speaker 0: Here's a copy of my resume.
Speaker 0: Have a seat, Mary.
Speaker 0: Thank you.
Speaker 1: Mary, do you have any experience working in the kitchen?
Speaker 0: No, but I want to learn.
Speaker 0: I work hard, and I cook a lot at home.
Speaker 1: OK.
Speaker 0: Well, tell me about yourself.
Speaker 0: Well, I love to learn new things.
Speaker 0: I'm very organized.
Speaker 0: And I follow directions exactly.
Speaker 0: That's why my boss at my last job made me a trainer.
Speaker 0: And the company actually gave me a special certificate for coming to work on time every day for a year.
Speaker 0: And I'm taking an English class to improve my writing skills.
Speaker 1: That's great.
Speaker 0: Why did you leave your last job?
Speaker 0: It was graveyard, and I need to work days.
Speaker 1: Oh, I see.
Speaker 0: Well, what hours can you work?
Speaker 0: From 8 AM until 5 PM.
Speaker 0: OK.
Speaker 0: Well, do you have any questions for me, Mary?
Speaker 0: Yes.
Speaker 0: What kind of training is needed?
Speaker 1: Not a lot.
Speaker 1: Most new workers can learn everything the first day.
Speaker 0: Do you have any other questions?
Speaker 0: No, I don't think so.
Speaker 0: But I've heard a lot of good things about your company, and I would really like to work here.
Speaker 0: Well, I have a few more interviews to do today.
Speaker 1: OK.
Speaker 1: But I will call you tomorrow if you get the job.
Speaker 0: OK.
Speaker 1: It was sure nice to meet you.
Speaker 0: Nice meeting you too.
Speaker 0: Thank you so much for your time.
Speaker 0: Yes, good luck.
Speaker 0: Thank you.